all right so for today's video I'm gonna
read a passage from the gifts of
imperfection and by brain Brown it's on
page 25 if you want to follow along most
of us use the terms fitting in and
belonging interchangeably and like many
of you I'm really good at fitting in we
know exactly how to hustle for approval
and acceptance we know what to wear what
to talk about how to make people happy
and what not to mention we know how to
chameleon our way through the day one of
the biggest surprises in this research
was learning that fitting in and
belonging are not the same thing and in
fact fitting in gets in the way of
belonging fitting in is about assessing
a situation and becoming who you need to
be to be accepted belonging on the other
hand doesn't require us to change who we
are
it requires us to be who we are that
giving people a space to belong starting
with the foundation that every human
being on this planet is worthy of a
connection and belonging and yet
foreseen belonging is fitting in in a
world where there's only one way to fit
in one way to belong to society it
requires you to change and therefore you
are not belonging you don't feel that
sense of connection and being seen we
can create that for one another both by
having an internal culture of acceptance
of not broken fake positivity oh yeah
I'd love it except you know you might be
worthy of loving connection and I might
not be capable of giving it to you
you might rub me the wrong way we might
not get it along at all but that doesn't
mean you can't be here and it doesn't
mean I
be there even if we can't necessarily be
at the same table everyone is worthy and
everyone can find a place to belong and
we can create the tools to make that
happen because we are gonna get so much
more innovation and so much more
creativity and discovery when we give
people a space to belong technology
seems like it's anti belonging because
we've used it as such on social media
it's all about fitting in you say one
thing wrong you get Doc's too bullied
and we have to make a culture that's
accepting of mistakes that has both
individually meaning we get to make
mistakes other people get to make
mistakes and as a whole together we're
gonna make mistakes and looking at how
do we help people make less mistakes if
they do do something that is truly wrong
how do we help them make it right
without shame without blame or by
minimizing those because that is what we
have done so far on this planet and it
has led to disconnection and addiction
and although most of us have clearly
been okay at fitting in it doesn't give
us a sense of belonging and that sense
of belonging empowers us to create all
of the change we are here to create that
is why our first project is gonna be one
of connection and communication because
is the foundation of everything that we
do creating a space that all you have to
do is bring yourself to the table
exactly as you are and if you can't get
along with other people exactly as you
are and exactly as they are we're gonna
figure that out together how do we
empower people to deal with conflict or
avoid conflict
it's an individual choice here tomorrow